QUARSHIE ISAAC

C/O Eric Kudor, P.O. Box CO 2162, Tema Community 8

Wesbite: https://www.youngquarshie.github.io

PROESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven Full Stack Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Built products for desktop and web apps over 2+ years. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web applications using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript and strong debugging and diagnostic skills.

EDUCATION

Valley View University

2018-2020

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (1st Class- C.G.P.A 3.77/4.00)

Koforidua Technical University

2015-2018

Higher National Diploma in Computer Science (1st Class- C.G.P.A 4.01/5.00)

PUBLICATION

Network Forensic Evaluation of Privacy Browsers - IJCT - Volume 7, Issue 4, No 2 / July-August 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, Go, VB.NET, C++ Frameworks: Twitter Bootstrap, CodeIgniter, CakePHP, Express Js, Next JS, and Node JS,

Angular JS, Angular, React, Ionic **Databases:** MySQL, PostgreSQL

CMS: Wordpress, WIX

Operating System: Linux, Windows

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AdaptiveBIBO LLC (North Carolina, USA)

Web Developer

March, 2020 – Present

• Built a Wordpress SMS plugin for Woocommerce and Contact Form 7 that automatically sends an SMS to the shop manager when an order is made by a customer.

- Made an update to a performance evaluation system that allowed users to upload an excel file using Angular JS, CodeIgniter and the PhpSpreadsheet Library.
- Set up a Content Delivery Network with Amazon Cloud Front that securely delivers data, videos, applications, and APIs to customers globally with low latency, high transfer speeds, all within a developer-friendly environment
- Incorporated a Single Sign on Authentication with Auth0 and Amazon Web Services that allows users to able to login with their preferred social media account.
- Developing websites with Wordpress.

Accolm Limited - Asylum Down, Accra

Web Developer

February, 2020 – March, 2020

Responsibilities:

• Collaborated with a team to build web apps using the CakePHP Framework to build a user-friendly content management system that allows clients to easily manage contents on their website.

Pesewa One – Adabraka, Accra

Full Stack Web Developer (Contract)

October, 2019 – November, 2020

• Collaborated with a team of 4 to build a web application using HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP that enables entrepreneurs to be able to find investors, employees, to manage the various operations of their business.

Social Security and National Insurance Trust (S.S.N.I. T) - Koforidua – Eastern Region National Service Personnel September, 2019 – September, 2020

- Managed and coordinated the conversion of various documents into electronic/digital format (scanning).
- Registration of New Members into the SSNIT Scheme to enable them to start making payments.
- Troubleshooted I.T Related issues such as fixing of network connectivity issues and fixing of printing error commands when the need arises
- Completed the Survivors Benefit Application Forms that enables the survivors to be able to receive payment
- Verified the Authenticity of Documents submitted by clients to prevent fraud.

Oxglow Analytics - Koforidua- Eastern Region

Jnr. Web Developer (Internship)

June, 2018 – July, 2018

- Assisted in the design, coding, and testing of technical solutions.
- Developed and implemented an interface design, and extensive data modelling to a modern database design and best practices.